siteimprove.com 2016-05-31

# Privacy Policy - Siteimprove

Effective: February 17, 2016

## INTRODUCTION

Siteimprove and its corporate affiliates (collectively, “ **Siteimprove** ”, “ **we** ”, “ **our** ” or “ **us** ”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through compliance with this Privacy Policy (the “ **Policy** ”).

This Policy describes: (i) the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide to us; and (ii) our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

This Policy applies to information we collect: on our website, siteimprove.com (the “Website”); in e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and us; through information and submissions that you provide to us, both online and offline; and when you interact with us through third-party websites and services (e.g., social networking providers) (collectively, the “Services”)

Each time that you access or use the Services, you signify that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, you must discontinue using the Services.

### The What: The Information We Collect About You

We collect the following type of information from you when you use our Services:

  * Information that personally identifies you (“ **Personal Information** ”). Personal Information includes your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number or any other identifier through which you may be contacted online or offline;
  * Information that is anonymous, aggregate, de-identified or otherwise does not reveal your identity (“ **Other Information** ”). This information can include details about your location, browser, internet connection, operating system, and behavior on the Services (e.g., clicks, time viewing a page).

## The When, The Where & The How: The Methods We Use to Collect the Information

This is how we collect information from you when you use our Services:

  * You directly provide it to us. Some ways in which you do this are: 
    * Creating a login for using Siteimprove;
    * Complete and submit online forms to us;
    * Report a problem to us;
    * Correspond with us;
    * Respond to our surveys; or
    * Post information through our Services.
  * You indirectly provide it to us. The primary way that this occurs is through automatic data collection technologies that collect statistical (non-personal) information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns to provide details about: 
    * Traffic data
    * Location and IP address
    * Communication data
    * Resources accessed on the Services
    * Operating System
    * Browser

The technologies we and the third parties (e.g., Hubspot) providing content and applications to the Services may use for this automatic data collection include:

  * **Cookies**. A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Services. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system may issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Services.
  * **Web Beacon** Pages of our Services and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit Siteimprove to, for example, count users who have visited a page or opened an e-mail.

### The Why: What We Do With This Information

Siteimprove will only use and disclose your Personal Information for the purpose for which you have provided it to us at determined at the time of collection or through your subsequent consent. We only disclose Personal Information to our affiliates and vendors so that we can fulfill our obligations to you, manage our business operations (e.g., customer relationship management (CRM) system, opt-in marketing database, customer service and support system) and for the following reasons:

  * Improving our services;
  * Providing you with information, products or services that you request from us;
  * Fulfilling any other purpose for which you provide the Personal Information;
  * Our own corporate transactions and reorganizations;
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

Siteimprove will retain your Personal Information for as long as needed based on the purpose for which you have given us the information. We will also retain and use your Personal Information as necessary to: comply with our legal obligations; resolve disputes; enforce our agreements; and protect the rights, property or safety of Siteimprove, our customers or others.

### The Above Sections Explain Our Use of Collected Information – What About Third Party Use of that Information?

Some of the Services are served by third-parties (e.g., HubSpot). These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Services. The information they collect may be associated with your Personal Information or they may collect information, including Personal Information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online service. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content. **We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used.** For that reason, you should read the privacy policies of every service that you use. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see “How You Can Limit Use and Disclosure of Your Information”.

How Do We Respond to Do Not Track Signals (CalOPPA Notice)?

We do not track you over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising. Therefore, we do not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals.

Some third parties providing content and applications to the Services does respond to DNT signals and that will limit your access to the interactive features of the Services.

In addition, Siteimprove does not authorize the collection of Personal Information from our website unless you opt-in to providing that information directly to the third party.

### How You Can Limit Use and Disclosure of Your Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the Personal Information you provide to us. Here are some mechanisms to provide you with control over your information:

  * **Promotional Offers from Siteimprove.** If you do not wish to have your e-mail address/contact information used by Siteimprove to promote our own services, you can opt-out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data or by sending us an e-mail stating your request to privacy@siteimprove.com. If we have sent you a promotional e-mail, you may send us a return e-mail asking to be omitted from future e-mail distributions.
  * **Targeted Ads By Third Parties.** We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative on its website: [www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

### How You Can Access and Correct Your Information

Siteimprove aims to keep Personal Information accurate and up to date. You may send us an e-mail at privacy@siteimprove.com to request access to, correct or delete any Personal Information that you have provided to us. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Services that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to privacy@siteimprove.com or write us at: Siteimprove; 8000 Norman Center Drive, Suite 300; Minneapolis, MN 55437; ATTN: Privacy Counsel.

We Do Not Collect Information From Children Under the Age of 13

Our Services are not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on the Services. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected or received Personal Information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at privacy@siteimprove.com.

### Details on Data Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. In addition, we have executed data-processing agreements and model contract clauses with many of our third-party vendors as a means of meeting the adequacy and security requirements of the European Parliament and Council of the European Union Data Protection Directive.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information transmitted to our Services. Any transmission of Personal Information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained in our Services.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to the Policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat Personal Information, we will notify you through a notice on our website’s home page. The date the Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for periodically visiting our Services and this Policy to check for any changes.

### Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this Policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:

Siteimprove

7807 Creekridge Circle  
Bloomington, MN 55439  
USA

ATTN: Privacy Counsel  
privacy@siteimprove.com
